Hugh Stanley

These are only the most recent and the very first projects I have worked on in my 39 years in the industry. I have also worked on many office, shop, hotel and other commercial fit outs as well as domestic housing contracts, initially employed as a joiner but latterly as a site manager/foreman, displaying skills including sourcing and ordering materials, client liason, health and safety management, program adherence and general foreman duties. I possess excellent timekeeping and attendace levels and have healthy man management skills. I enjoy task and problem solving.

Whilst possessing good computing skills I am also conversant with producing and editing CAD drawing

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Aug 2015— present
Oracle Interiors
Various Shopfits throughout UK

March 2015—June 2015
Oracle Interiors
Oxford St, London
Shopfit of Ecco Flagship store

Oct 2014—Feb 2015
Oracle Interiors
Stafford
Fit out of KRM Showrooms

May 2014– Sept 2014 Oracle Interiors London Fit out of Hermes Store

Jan 2014 - May 2014 Oracle Interiors Cheltenam Shopfit Ecco store

Aug 2013– Nov 2103 Kiwi Interiors Manchester Fit out of JD Sports store

May 2013 —July 2013 Brydol Bank Fashion Shopfit of Bank fashion store in Wrexham

18 Buckingham Road Droylsden Manchester M43 6WA

Phone: 0161-371 9372 Mob: 07940730398 E-mail: h-stanley@live.co.uk Mar 2013-April 2013 Prime Design

(Nestle Gatwick)

Fit out and installation of professional kitchens (sensory booths, serverys, coffee tasting counters etc).

Hugh Stanley

Aug 1979-82

Manchester City Council Indentured apprentice in Carpentry & Joinery

EDUCATION:

QUALIFICATIONS:

St Gregory's Grammar 1974-1979

Maths A
English B
History C
Woodwork B
G.E.D B
Biology C
English Literature C

Manchester College of Building 1979-1982

City & Guilds Carpentry & Joinery

Ordinary Craft Advanced Craft

The Manchester College 1998-1999

NVQ level 2 Computer

Aided Design

Tameside College 2014– 2016 Cert Ed in Teaching in the

Lifelong Learning Sector

Health & Safety Asbestos Awarness Cert

CSCS card SSSTS First Aid Cert

REFERENCES:

Gary Horton Oracle Interiors Lysander Way Salisbury Wiltshire SP4 6BU 07919028978

Mr David Walsh 44 Selby Street Bradford Manchester M11 2AY 07949776903

18 Buckingham Road Droylsden Manchester M43 6WA

Phone: 0161-371 9372 Mob: 07940730398 E-mail: h-stanley@live.co.uk

INTERESTS:

Sailing, Ski-ing, Tennis, Travel